Hello friends, welcome again.
Before your appointment, you should also check the old videos. There are
some opportunities for you there. You
can apply by going to them. Our
video will be a little long but the
complete details will be clearly mentioned on it and no
charge of any kind is
taken from any candidate. 100% genuine jobs are
provided. Friends, those who have
not liked and subscribed or those who are new
viewers, please tell them to like and
subscribe the channel so that notifications
reach you and some other candidate can get selected for the job through you.
Friends, first of all let's talk about
what vacancies we are going to have.
Friends, here we need a relationship
manager. So what is ICICI Lombard? It
provides insurance. So, you
need a company to have a relationship manager. Some
relationship executives, relationship manager
profile
candidates. What will be their work? They will
call the existing customers of ICICI and will
give them details about their product on the call. They will
share details about ICICI Lombard with them etc. First of all let's talk about what is in it.
What is the qualification
required friends friends here the
qualification that matters to us is that
we should be a 12th pass candidate
but in the final year of graduation
or a complete graduate yes
friends I am repeating that if you are
not a complete 12th pass then you should be a graduate in the final year
in graduation subject and then you should be a graduate
this is mandatory here
qualification do not skip
watch the entire video it is possible that
someone else may get a job through you you can share it with them
if you like the video then let's talk
here from salary point of view
friends here the salary company is providing very good salary
from 25000 to 31000
here along with
other benefits which are your
brand name so there will be some
profit in it also the company provides insurance up to 20 lakhs
Apart from that, there is an incentive part for its employees, the
annual bonus from the company
is Diwali bonus, so
all these things are included in this, so one salary gets
converted into an attractive salary,
along with this you are getting the benefit
that you are joining such a brand
where you will get to learn something good
and when you go to any other
company with your job, you will be asked about your last experience there too, so when you
explain it, it will have a
great impact on the company as well,
friends let's talk about what their job
timing is going to be, friends, it is going to be a Monday
to Saturday job, your Sunday will be fixed
here, yes friends, it will
be a fixed off, it is a Monday to Saturday office
timing job, your job time is from 9 to 6 to 10, including breaks,
tea
breaks etc., all that is there, let's
talk about this fresher experience
candidate, friends, if you have worked
in ICICI or in any company, you  If you have
worked in an insurance background, then
your six months'
experience will also be accepted here. If you have done six months'
experience in any insurance field, then
you are eligible there.
Friends, this position is limited for us.
We have demand for only 50 candidates. If there is a
demand for 50 candidates, then
candidates who generally have
experience in this field should apply. Secondly,
if your experience is from another field, if
you have worked in any other profile, then
also you can apply here,
but your background should be
of voice. You should have a background of voice process. If you have
worked in any such process, then
your experience should be of at least one year.
Now let's talk about how this experience will be
counted. So you
should have documentation,
like experience letter, salary slips, etc. Now
see, if the company is a big MNC company, then
your experience there should also be accordingly.  You will have to
show it only if you only
show experience without documents, then that
experience does not matter in big
companies, it is acceptable in small companies
where no one notices the
experience, but if you
apply in a big company then take care of the experience letter,
friends, let's talk about
what is required here communication wise, so
friends, excellent communication
skills are required here, very good English is
required, so you can share this video with any of your friends
who speak English well,
we try to bring every type of
job for you people,
but mostly we have those
jobs in which there is bulk hiring,
which we are not closing quickly
or in which we require a lot of numbers
or the company has a lot of demand,
first of all
check those in the description box, our
team numbers are given, if you have
excellent English, you are speaking very good English,
then you
can check in the comment box given below, you can call the team,
that is your  We will schedule the interview etc.
Friends, for our today
's vacancy and similar latest updates,
like and subscribe to our channel
and keep sharing it with your friend circle
because it is possible that
someone else may get a job through you. I will meet
you again friends with a new video, till then bye bye.